Presented by Viki
Vikiのエンジニアリング.
私たちは、世界中のテレビの未来を再構築します。
私たちは何者か
Vikiのエンジニアチームは viki.com の裏側で開発と保守に取り組んでいます。グローバルTVサイトは熱心なファンのコミュニティによって支えられています。
Launched in December 2010, we have over 2 billion video streams and more than 400 million words translated.
We are not obsessed by any particular technology.
We believe cool technologies might not get the job done, the right technologies do.
We use Ruby, Node.js, Golang, AngularJS, EmberJS with PostgreSQL, Redis and RabbitMQ.
We make sure our code are highly decoupled through message queue infrastructure, service-oriented architectures and proper design patterns.